Guide to the Robert O. Pohl papers, 1973-1998
Pohl, Robert O. papers, 1973-1998
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Robert O. Pohl papers, 1973-1998.
14-22-3253
Robert O. Pohl
27 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reference files, clippings, published reportsl, studies.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files include correspondence relating to Pohl's sabbatic leave, research including communications with international colleagues and correspondence with his graduate students; notes on energy which comprise reference files of clippings and handwritten notations; published reports on nuclear waste and waste sites, contaminated and non-contaminated sites, high-level nuclear waste disposal, reactor decommissioning, reactor accidents, radiation health effects, EPA studies and specific sites of radwaste contaminiation, carbon dioxide, thermal studies in high-level waste disposal,and uranuium mill tailings.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Physicist.
Robert O. Pohl received the Ph.D. in Physics from the University of Erlangen in Germany in 1957. He joined the Cornell faculty in 1958 in the Department of Physics and the Laboratory of Atomic and Solid State Physics. In 1984, Pohl was awarded the Oliver E. Buckley Solid State Physics Prize of the American Physical Society for his work on the structure of glass and glassy materials. In addition to his basic research, Professor Pohl has been interested in issues relating to nuclear waste disposal, serving on President Carter's advisory committee.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files include correspondence relating to Pohl's sabbatic leave, research including communications with international colleagues and correspondence with his graduate students; notes on energy which comprise reference files of clippings and handwritten notations; published reports on nuclear waste and waste sites, contaminated and non-contaminated sites, high-level nuclear waste disposal, reactor decommissioning, reactor accidents, radiation health effects, EPA studies and specific sites of radwaste contaminiation, carbon dioxide, thermal studies in high-level waste disposal,and uranuium mill tailings.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pohl, Robert O.; Cornell University.Dept. of Physics.; Nuclear Waste Program (U.S.)
Subjects:
Radioactive waste disposal.; Radioactive wastes--Environmental aspects.; Radioactive wastes--Management.; Radioactive wastes--Safety regulations.; Physicists.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Notes on Energy
  - Federal Register EPA, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Air, Water Standards, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Radiation Standards, 1959-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Radiation Standards, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Radiation Standards, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Radiation Standards, 1959-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Low Level Effects, 1975-1984 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Low Level Effects, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Low Level Effects, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Low Level Effects, 1974-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Low Level Effects, 1974-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - German Standards, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - German Standards, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Risks of Nuclear Power, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Environmental Radiation Protection, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Routine Emissions, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Routine Emissions, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Routine Emissions, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Occupational Exposure at Reactors, 1975-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Occupational Exposure at Reactors, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Plutonium/Transplutonium, 1974-1984 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Iodine, 1975-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Plutonium, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Plutonium, 1966-1979 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Plutonium, 1974-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Plutonium, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - ECCS & Rasmussen, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - ECCS & Rasmussen, 1972-1979 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - ECCS & Rasmussen, 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Disasters, 1975-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Disasters, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Four Accidents, 1977-1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Four Accidents, 1969-1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Four Accidents, 1968-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Four Accidents, 1972-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sabotage & Attack, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cooling Systems, 1972-1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Siting, 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Diversion of SNM, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1976-1980 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Nuclear Industry, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Waste Disposal, 1978-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Changing to Nuclear Power, 1951-1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1967-1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1965-1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Public Opinion & Debate, 1972-1976 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Decontamination, 1970-1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Decontamination, 1972-1985 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Decommissioning, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Pohl's Research, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Decommissioning, 1969-1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Decommissioning, 1974-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Decommissioning, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Decommissioning, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Uranium Resources, 1973-1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Land Use, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Brine Migration, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Brine Migration, 1972-1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1971-1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1971-1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1976-1979 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1970-1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1975-1978 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1973-1975 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1974-1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Burial of Low-level Nuclear Waste, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Land and Sea Disposal of Nuclear Waste, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1953-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Newspaper Clippings on Nuclear Waste, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1968-1974 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tucson Nuclear Waste Management, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pittman on Nuclear Waste Management, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Enrichment Technology, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Net Energy, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Fusion, 1971-1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Fusion, 1970-1976 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Energy Forecasts, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Energy Forecasts, 1977-1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - An Analysis of Federal Incentives Used to Stimulate Energy Production, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Energy Information Administration's Annual Report to Congress, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Projection of Nuclear Power Growth in the U.S., 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Projection of Nuclear Power Growth in the U.S., 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Projection of Nuclear Power Growth in the U.S., 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Federal Contracting & Regulation, 1972-1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - State Contracting & Regulation, 1972-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Private Contracting, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Utilities in NY, 1970-1980 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Nuclear Power Policies of Foreign Countries, 1975-1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Nuclear Power Policies of Foreign Countries, 1972-1978 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Nuclear Power Foreign Policy, 1974-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Enrichment Subsidies, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Breeder Reactors, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Breeder Reactors, 1967-1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Breeder Reactors, 1972-1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Breeder Reactors, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Gas Reactors, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Uranium Production, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Uranium Production, 1975-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Air Pollution, Power Plants, 1974-1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Effect of Air Pollution on Plants, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Effect of Air Pollution on Plants, 1976-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Effect of Air Pollution on Plants, 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Air Pollution and Its Effect on Plants, Power Plants, 1972-1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Proceedings of a Conference on Emerging Environmental Problems: Acid Precipitation, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Air Pollution and Its Effects on Human Health and Plants, 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Air Pollution, EPA Regulations, Power Plants, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Papers on Renewable Energy Sources and Nuclear/Coal Economics, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Air Pollution, Power Plants, Inhaber Report, 1977-1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Nuclear vs. Coal, 1975-1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear vs. Coal, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear vs. Coal, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear vs. Coal, 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Utility Capacity, 1973-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Utility Capacity, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Worker Plutonium Exposure, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - International Nuclear Power, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing, 1954-1975 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing, 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correlation of Radioactive Waste Treatment Costs and the Environmental Impact of Waste Effluents in the Nuclear Fuel Cycle-Reprocessing of High-Temperature Gas-Cooled Reactor Fuel Containing U-233 and Thorium, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Air Pollution from Nuclear Power, 1972-1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - German Publications regarding Nuclear Power, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Air Pollution from Nuclear Power, German Publications, 1966-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Carbon-14 and Nuclear Power, 1964-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Carbon-14 and Nuclear Power, 1963-1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Carbon-14 and Nuclear Power, 1958-1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Carbon-14 and Nuclear Power, 1959-1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Testing and Fallout, 1958-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1950-1982 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1947-1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1966-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Peaceful Nuclear Explosions, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Peaceful, Non-energy Nuclear Uses, 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - The Nuclear Fuel Cycle, 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Power and Economics, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Energy Crisis and Nuclear Power, 1957-1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Weinberg's Views on Nuclear Energy, 1954-1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Weinberg's Views on Nuclear Energy, 1971-1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Stand und Moglichkeiten der Energie-Direktumwandlung, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Oil, 1973-1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Fluidized-bed Combustion, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Coal, 1972-1981 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Natural Gas, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Coal Gasification, 1974-1979 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Oil Shale, Tar Sands, 1974-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Hydroelectric Power, 1978-1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Solar Energy, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - The Solar Market: Proceedings of the Symposium on Competition in the Solar Energy Industry, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Solar Energy, 1978-1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Solar Energy, 1973-1980 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Solar Energy, 1964-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Solar Energy, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Solar Energy, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Solar Energy, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Solar Energy, 1972-1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Photovoltaic Energy Sources, 1951-1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Wind Power, 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Geothermal Energy, 1972-1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Hydroelectric Power, 1966-1978 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Natural Gas, Methanol, Wood, and Photosynthesis as Energy, 1973-1979 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Crazy Inventions, 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NYSEG's application to build a power plant in Lansing, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Energy Conservation: Heating & Cooling, 1966-1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Energy Conservation: Transportation, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Energy Conservation: General, 1974-1980 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Energy Conservation: General, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Energy Conservation: General, 1972-1979 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Statistics on Energy Consumption, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Chromium, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Climatic Effects, 1967-1979 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Climatic Effects, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Climatic Effects, 1956-1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Energy Storage & Transmission, 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Ash Use & Disposal, 1972-1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Energy Crisis & Policy, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Energy Crisis & Policy, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Energy Crisis & Policy, 1970-1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pollutants, 1971-1978 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pollutants, 1974-1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mercury Pollution, 1971-1979 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Environmental Problems & Policy, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Environmental Problems & Policy, 1961-1979 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Problems & Policy: Love Canal, 1976-1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Ozone Layer Depletion, 1974-1978 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - The Energy Crisis, Population & Food Supply, 1972-1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Fuel Scarcity and Economic Growth, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Energy Conversion and Engineering Conference, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, 1973-1978 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Disposal of Hazardous Waste, 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Disposal of Hazardous Waste, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Disposal of Hazardous Waste, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Disposal of Hazardous Waste, 1977-1979 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Status of Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing Spent Fuel Storage and High-Level Waste Disposal, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1978-1979 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1977-1980 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1972-1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1975-1979 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Waste Management, 1979-1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Office of Nuclear Waste Isolation's Technical Progress Report for the Quarter April 1-June 30, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Pacific Northwest Laboratory's Progress Reports regarding Nuclear Waste Research, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Nuclear Waste, 1978-1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Geothermal Alteration of Clay Minerals and Shales: Diagenesis, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Radon, Uranium Mining & Milling, 1973-1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Radon, Uranium Mining & Milling, 1971-1980 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Uranium Mine & Mill Tailings, Various Correspondence, 1975-1982 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Radon, Uranium Mine & Mill Tailings, 1964-1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, 1975-1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, Various Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, Various Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Uranium Milling, 1977-1979 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Radium, Uranium Mill Tailings, 1976-1979 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Power Plants and Pollutants, 1964-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Radon, Radium, Uranium, 1970-1979 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Radon, 1966-1978 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, Radon, Radioactivity in Construction Materials, 1975-1978 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Series II. Published Reports on Nuclear Waste
  - Alternatives for Managing Wastes from Reactors and Post-Fission Operations in the LWR Fuel Cycle (Box 13)
    - Vol. 1: Summary, Alternatives for the Back End of the LWR Fuel Cycle, Types and Properties of LWR Fuel Cycle Wastes, Projections of Waste Quantities, Selected Glossary (Box 13)
    - Vol. 2: Alternatives for Waste Treatment (Box 13)
    - Vol. 3: Alternatives for Interim Storage and Transportation (Box 13)
    - Vol. 4: Alternatives for Waste Isolation and Disposal (Box 13)
    - Vol. 5: Appendices (Box 13)
  - Alternative Processes for Managing Existing Commercial High-Level Radioactive Wastes (Box 13)
  - Final Generic Environmental Statement on the Use of Recycle Plutonium in Mixed Oxide Fuel in Light Water Cooled Reactors Executive Summary Vol. 1-5 (Box 13)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Statement on 10 CFR Part 61 "Licensing Requirements for Land Disposal of Radioactive Waste", September 1981 (Box 13)
    - Vol. 1: Summary (Box 13)
    - Vol. 2: Main Report (Box 13)
    - Vol. 3: Appendices A-F (Box 13)
    - Vol. 4: Appendices G-Q (Box 13)
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement on Management of Commercially Generated Radioactive Waste October 1980 (Box 13)
    - Vol. 1: Report (Box 13)
    - Vol. 2: Appendices (Box 13)
    - Vol. 3: Public Comments, Hearing Board Report (Box 13)
  - Subgroup Report on Alternative Technology Strategies for the Isolation of Nuclear Waste, Draft, October 1978 (Box 13)
  - Report to the President by the Insurgency Review Group on Nuclear Waste Management, March 1979 (Box 13)
  - Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing and High-Level Waste Disposal, An Interim Report, July 1977 (Box 13)
  - Endlagerung Radioaktiver Abfälle, Jahresbericht 1969, November 1970 (Box 13)
  - Endlagerung Radioaktiver Abfälle, Jahresbericht 1971, July 1972 (Box 13)
  - Appendix 17: Technical Status of the Radioactive Waste Repository - A Demonstration Project for Solid Radioactive Waste Disposal (Box 13)
  - Proposed Rules. Federal Register, Vol. 51, No. 118, June 19, 1986 (Box 13)
  - State of Geological Knowledge Regarding Potential Transport of High-Level Radioactive Waste From Deep Continental Repositories (Box 14)
  - Assessment of Waste Management of Volatile Radionuclides (Box 14)
  - Alternative Disposal Concepts for High-Level and Transuranic Radioactive Waste Disposal (Box 14)
  - Technical Support of Standards for High-Level Radioactive Waste Management March-August 1977: Task B March 1980: (Box 14)
    - Vol. A: Source Term Characterization (Box 14)
    - Vol. B: Engineering Controls (Box 14)
    - Vol. C: Migration Pathways (Box 14)
    - Vol. D: Release Mechanisms (Box 14)
  - A Classification System for Radioactive Waste Disposal-What Waste Goes Where?, June 1978 (Box 14)
  - Geoscience Data Base Handbook for Modeling a Nuclear Waste Repository Vol. 1 & 2, January 1981 (Box 14)
  - Nuclear Waste Management Technical Support in the Development of Nuclear Waste Form Criteria for the NRC, February 1982 (Box 14)
    - Vol. 1: Waste Package Overview (Box 14)
    - Vol. 2: Alternative TRU Technologies (Box 14)
    - Vol. 3: Waste Inventory Review (Box 14)
    - Vol. 4: Test Development Review (Box 14)
    - Vol. 5: National Waste Package Program (Box 14)
  - Review of DOE Waste Package Program Vol. 1: National Waste Package Program, February 1982 (Box 14)
  - Population Risks from Disposal of High-Level Radioactive Wastes in Geologic Repositories, Draft, December 1982 (Box 14)
  - Draft Environmental Statement for 40 CFR 191: Environmental Standards for Management and Disposal of Spent Nuclear Fuel, High-Level and Transuranic Radioactive Wastes, December 1982 (Box 14)
  - Environmental Pathway Models for Estimating Population Health Effects from Disposal of High-Level Radioactive Waste in Geologic Repositories, Draft, December 1982 (Box 14)
  - Background Information Document: Proposed Standards for Radionuclides, Draft, March 1983 (Box 14)
  - EPA 40 CFR Part 61: National Emissions Standards for Hazardous Air Pollutants; Proposed Standards for Radionuclides, March 29, 1983 (Box 14)
  - Technical Assistance for Regulatory Development: Review and Evaluation of the Draft EPA Standard 40CFR191 for Disposal of High-Level Waste Vol. 1: Executive Summary, April 1983 (Box 14)
  - High-Level and Transuranic Radioactive Wastes, Background Information, Document for Final Rule, August 1985 (Box 14)
  - The Federal Nuclear Energy Program: A Synopsis, January 1983 (Box 15)
  - Integrated Radwaste Treatment System: Lessons Learned from 2 1/2 Years of Operation, May 1997 (Box 15)
  - Waste Materials in the United States Atomic Energy Program, January 12, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Spent Fuel and Radioactive Waste Inventories, Projections, and Characteristics, October 1982 (Box 15)
  - The Characteristics of Spent LWR Fuel Relevant to its Storage in Geologic Repositories (Box 15)
  - Integrated Data Base for 1987, 1989-93: U.S. Spent Fuel and Radioactive Waste Inventories, Projections, and Characteristics (Box 15)
  - Integrated Data Base Report - 1993-95: U.S. Spent Fuel and Radioactive Waste Inventories, Projections, and Characteristics (Box 15)
  - Perspektiven der Kernenergie: Vorträge eines Seminars veranstaltet von der Programmgruppe Kernenergie und Umwelt der Kernforschungsanlage Jülich GmbH (Box 15)
  - Report of the Cornell Workshops on the Major Issues of a National Energy Research and Development Program (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Power and the Environment: Questions and Answers (Box 15)
  - Geological Criteria for Repositories for High-Level Radioactive Wastes (Box 15)
  - Rethinking High-Level Radioactive Waste Disposal (Box 15)
  - Nuclear Waste Isolation Activities Report, May 1980 (Box 15)
  - Integrated Data Base Program (Box 15)
  - A Guidebook to Nuclear Reactors (Box 15)
  - Living Without Landfills, a Special Report by the Radioactive Waste Campaign (Box 15)
  - Deadly Defense: Military Radioactive Landfills (Box 15)
  - Program Summary: Nuclear Waste Management and Fuel Cycle Programs, July 1982 (Box 15)
  - Memorandum to Dennis M. Crutchfield from Charles S. Hinson, re: LWR Occupational Dose Data for 1994, December 26, 1995 (Box 15)
  - A Study of the Isolation System for Geologic Disposal of Radioactive Wastes (Box 15)
  - Report to the Congress by the Comptroller General of the United States: Federal Facilities for Storing Spent Nuclear Fuel: Are They Needed?, June 27, 1979 (Box 15)
  - The Disposal of Radioactive Waste on Land: Report of the Committee on Waste Disposal of the Division of Earth Sciences, September 1957 (Box 15)
  - Preliminary Pre-Emplacement Safety Analysis of the Subseabed Disposal of High-Level Nuclear Waste, January 1985 (Box 15)
  - Disposal of Liquid Radioactive Wastes Through Wells or Shafts (Box 15)
  - Defense Transuranic Waste Program Strategy Document, July 1982 (Box 15)
  - Overview Assessment of Nuclear Waste Management (Box 15)
  - Evaluation of Research and Development for Terminal Isolation of Nuclear Wastes (Box 15)
  - Developing Criteria for the Management of Nuclear Wastes (Box 15)
  - Underground Storage: A Worldwide Summary (Box 16)
  - National Waste Terminal Storage Program Progress Report, for period April 1, 1975 to September 30, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Determination of Performance Criteria for High-Level Solidified Nuclear Waste, July 1977 (Box 16)
  - Essays on Issues Relevant to the Regulation of Radioactive Waste Management, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Radioactive Waste in Geologic Storage, 1979 (Box 16)
  - Information Base for Waste Repository Design, March 1979 (Box 16)
    - Vol. 1 :Borehole and Shaft Sealing (Box 16)
    - Vol. 2: Equipment Performance Requirements (Box 16)